const data = [
  {
    question: "Who was the highest run-scorer in the 2019 ICC Cricket World Cup?",
    option1: "David Warner",
    option2: "Rohit Sharma",
    option3: "Kane Williamson",
    option4: "Shakib Al Hasan",
    ans: "Rohit Sharma"
  },
  {
    question: "Which bowler took the most wickets in the 2015 ICC Cricket World Cup?",
    option1: "Mitchell Starc",
    option2: "Trent Boult",
    option3: "Umesh Yadav",
    option4: "Morne Morkel",
    ans: "Mitchell Starc"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the first player to score a double century in a World Cup match?",
    option1: "Chris Gayle",
    option2: "Martin Guptill",
    option3: "Rohit Sharma",
    option4: "Virender Sehwag",
    ans: "Martin Guptill"
  },
  {
    question: "Which team won the inaugural ICC World Test Championship in 2021?",
    option1: "India",
    option2: "Australia",
    option3: "New Zealand",
    option4: "England",
    ans: "New Zealand"
  },
  {
    question: "Who holds the record for the fastest century in ODI cricket as of 2024?",
    option1: "AB de Villiers",
    option2: "Corey Anderson",
    option3: "Shahid Afridi",
    option4: "Chris Gayle",
    ans: "AB de Villiers"
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the Player of the Tournament in the 2016 ICC T20 World Cup?",
    option1: "Virat Kohli",
    option2: "Joe Root",
    option3: "Marlon Samuels",
    option4: "Carlos Brathwaite",
    ans: "Virat Kohli"
  },
  {
    question: "Who became the fastest bowler to reach 100 ODI wickets in 2019?",
    option1: "Mitchell Starc",
    option2: "Rashid Khan",
    option3: "Trent Boult",
    option4: "Jasprit Bumrah",
    ans: "Rashid Khan"
  },
  {
    question: "Which cricketer broke the record for the most sixes in an ODI inning in 2018?",
    option1: "Chris Gayle",
    option2: "Rohit Sharma",
    option3: "Eoin Morgan",
    option4: "AB de Villiers",
    ans: "Eoin Morgan"
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the captain of the winning team in the 2017 ICC Champions Trophy?",
    option1: "Eoin Morgan",
    option2: "Virat Kohli",
    option3: "Sarfraz Ahmed",
    option4: "Faf du Plessis",
    ans: "Sarfraz Ahmed"
  },
  {
    question: "Which player scored the fastest T20I century as of 2024?",
    option1: "David Miller",
    option2: "Rohit Sharma",
    option3: "Chris Gayle",
    option4: "Suryakumar Yadav",
    ans: "David Miller"
  }
];
export default data;
